{"data":[{"question":"You will see a bowl of flowers or a long silk paintings on one of the walls.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"One","b":"difficulties","c":"for","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"You may be surprised seeing that there are no bedrooms.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"good","c":"from","d":"on","answer":"4","explain":"- On->in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"One of the greatest difficulties for foreign students in American universities are the lecture system.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first","b":"to learn","c":"more","d":"whole","answer":"3","explain":"- More-> most","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"It is not easy to take good notes from a lecture on a foreign language.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"early","b":"with","c":"hard","d":"to bring","answer":"2","explain":"- With-> and","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The first skill to learn is how to write only the more important words, not whole sentences.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"learnt","b":"to read","c":"in","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"- In-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Her mother died early with her father tried hard to bring up the four children.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"hard","c":"became","d":"physicists","answer":"4","explain":"- physicists-> physicist","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Marie learnt to read and write in the age of four.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was having","b":"at","c":"when","d":"was coming","answer":"4","explain":"- Was coming-> came","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"She worked very hard and became a famous chemist and physicists.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"understand","b":"to speak","c":"when","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"- To speak-> speak","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Jim was having dinner at a restaurant when Henry was coming in.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"official","c":"one-fifths","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"- One-fifths-> one-fifth","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"He could understand algebra and to speak French when he was six.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many","b":"taught","c":"even though","d":"native","answer":"2","explain":"- Taught-> teach","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}